https://tylerbankruptcylawyer.com/privacy-policy/

Bankruptcy Information
Why File Bankruptcy?
Why Hire a Bankruptcy Attorney
Bankruptcy Basics
Myths About Bankruptcy
Will Business Bankruptcy Ruin My Personal Credit?
FILING BANKRUPTCY A SECOND TIME
What Debts Are Dischargeable?
Bankruptcy Exemptions
What is the Wildcard Exemption?
Small Business Bankruptcy
Can Bankruptcy Save My Business?
Bankruptcy Traps: What Not To Do
Will Business Bankruptcy Ruin My Personal Credit?
Privacy Policy
What Information Do We Collect?
We collect information from you when you fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To process transactions
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes To Our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
HomeSmith County Bankruptcy InformationSmith County Bankruptcy LawyerTexas Bankruptcy BlogTyler Bankruptcy OfficePrivacy PolicySitemap
